Once I was dead, I lived for self
Offending God, ignoring Him
I walked the world’s dark crooked ways
Deceived by lies and empty praise
I bowed my heart to selfish pride
My cravings ruled, they were my guide
But Christ so rich in mercy’s grace
He paid my sin and took my place
His love so great, so deep, so high
He raised me up, I'll never die
He took my soul from death’s dark helm
Now seated with Christ in heaven’s realm
Oh-oh, immeasurable grace
Oh-oh, how glorious Your ways
Oh-oh, forever I'll praise
Your goodness in Christ
Your mercy that saves
Your immeasurable grace
I followed darkness, so blind and proud
A voice within the rebel crowd
I lived to feed my flesh and mind
No thought of God, no truth to find
By nature I deserved His wrath
Stumbling down a fatal path
But God displayed His richest grace
A love that time will not erase
By grace through faith, not by my doing
The gift of God, my boast removing
In Jesus Christ I’ve been remade
For the good works which God ordained
Oh-oh, immeasurable grace
Oh-oh, how glorious Your ways
Oh-oh, forever I'll praise
Your goodness in Christ
Your mercy that saves
Your immeasurable grace
From death to life, You called my name
Now I’m alive to praise Your name
No longer lost, no longer bound
In Christ alone, I’ve been made found
Oh-oh, immeasurable grace
Oh-oh, how glorious Your ways
Oh-oh, forever I'll praise
Your goodness in Christ
Your mercy that saves
Your immeasurable grace
Immeasurable grace, unfailing and true
Forever I’ll live to worship You
To sing of your immeasurable grace
Immeasurable grace